lang{	Language	English		Tokens	{		// HUD		FORTRESS_HUD_HEALTH		"HEALTH"		FORTRESS_HUD_RESOURCES	"RESOURCES"			// Teams		FORTRESS_ALIENS					"Aliens"		FORTRESS_HUMANS					"Humans"				// Team Selection		FORTRESS_TEAMHEADER				"Team Selection"		FORTRESS_TEAMHUMANINFO			"The Humans aren't quite technically advanced compared to their adversaries, but they make up for it with cheaper equipment and faster respawn times."		FORTRESS_TEAMALIENINFO			"The Aliens are highly advanced, however their equipment is more costly and takes longer to produce."		FORTRESS_TEAMAUTOINFO			"Automatically assign yourself to the most appropriate team."				// Class Selection		FORTRESS_RECONDESCRIPTION		"Can unlock radar scanning technology to detect enemies on the minimap within a limited range. Armed with dual semi-automatic pistols and a sticky grenade. Has a jetpack that can be upgraded. Very fast and quick.(Placeholder desc)"		FORTRESS_COMMANDODESCRIPTION	"Can kick enemies down to the ground when close to them, armed with a Burst Rifle and a Power Shield. Has Adrenalin rush ability that makes you and your teammates within a limited range around you faster and more resistant to bullets.(placeholder desc)"		FORTRESS_MEDICDESCRIPTION		"Armed with a Combat Shotgun and a Repair gun, this class can heal buildings and teammates. He can build an Autorepair and a Self-heal. (Placeholder desc)"		FORTRESS_DEFENDERDESCRIPTION	"Armed with a Minigun. Can build sentry guns and has limpet mines. Slow but effective for plowing down enemies. Also has a power shield. (Placeholder desc)"		FORTRESS_SNIPERDESCRIPTION		"Armed with a Sniper Rifle. Can cloak when standing still as well. Good for quickly and instantly killing players in the way if you're skilled enough. (Placeholder desc)"		FORTRESS_CLASSPYROINFO			"Armed with a Flamethrower and a Gas can, can light gas on fire to create traps. Also has a Grenade Launcher. (Placeholder desc)"		FORTRESS_INFILTRATORDESCRIPTION	"Armed with a knife and a pistol. Can cloak and disguise as enemy players and could gain corpse-consuming technology which allows you to play dead as enemy corpses. (Placeholder desc)"		FORTRESS_SAPPERDESCRIPTION		"Can build Sentry Guns, Buff Station, and an EMP Generator. Armed with a Drainbeam, a weapon that is the complete opposite of the Repair gun. It drains enemy health and charges an EMP that will be sent to the player you were draining. Also armed with Rallyflags, a device that emits Adrenalin towards nearby players that increases their health and damage resistance within a limited range. (Placeholder desc)"		FORTRESS_ESCORTDESCRIPTION		"Has a huge shield around him that other team players can enter to gain cover. Armed with a Burst Rifle. (Placeholder desc)"		FORTRESS_SUPPORTDESCRIPTION		"An alternative to the Defender that can push back enemy players and keep them out of the way, or suppress them. Armed with a Plasma Rifle. Good for pushing enemy players back at the cost of having low health. (Placeholder desc)"		FORTRESS_CLASSRANDOMINFO		"The game will choose a random class for you"				// Vehicles		INVASION_OBJECT_WALKER			"Walker"		INVASION_OBJECT_MINIWALKER		"Mini Walker"		INVASION_OBJECT_WAGON			"Wagon"		INVASION_OBJECT_BATTERINGRAM	"Battering Ram"		INVASION_OBJECT_TANK			"Tank"		INVASION_OBJECT_TELEPORTSTATION	"Teleport Station"				// Vehicle Bay		INVASION_VEHICLEBAY_TITLE	"Vehicle Bay"		Game_connected			"%s1 connected"		Game_disconnected		"%s1 has left the game"	}}